export const data = [
  {
    question: "Which keyword is used for defining a function in Python?",
    option1: "def",
    option2: "function",
    option3: "define",
    option4: "func",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the result of 2 + 3 * 4?",
    option1: "20",
    option2: "18",
    option3: "14",
    option4: "10",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following is a Python data type?",
    option1: "Float",
    option2: "String",
    option3: "Character",
    option4: "All of the above",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the output of 'hello'[1:]?",
    option1: "hello",
    option2: "h",
    option3: "ello",
    option4: "e",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Which function is used to get user input in Python?",
    option1: "input()",
    option2: "get_input()",
    option3: "user_input()",
    option4: "read_input()",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the correct way to create an empty list in Python?",
    option1: "list = []",
    option2: "list = {}",
    option3: "list = ()",
    option4: "list = None",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following is a Python library for data manipulation and analysis?",
    option1: "Pandas",
    option2: "Numpy",
    option3: "Matplotlib",
    option4: "All of the above",
    ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the output of 2**3?",
    option1: "8",
    option2: "6",
    option3: "5",
    option4: "10",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which loop in Python is used to iterate over a sequence?",
    option1: "for",
    option2: "while",
    option3: "do-while",
    option4: "foreach",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the 'len()' function return in Python?",
    option1: "Length of an object",
    option2: "Type of an object",
    option3: "Maximum value of an object",
    option4: "Minimum value of an object",
    ans: 1,
  },
];
